https://www.hennsnoxlaw.com/privacy-policy-1

About UsFirm HistoryCommunity InvolvementNewsEventsFor BusinessesCorporate LawConstruction LawCreditor's RightsEmployment LawLicensingNonprofit LawCommercial Real EstateTrademarks & CopyrightsLitigationFor IndividualsFamily Law and DivorceElder LawEstate PlanningResidential Real EstateAttorneysJames E. SnoxellSteven M. GraffunderJeffrey A. BergMark V. SteffensonCraig T. DokkenSusan T. Peterson-LerdahlChad E. HendersonDebra NelsonTifanne WolterAdam J. KaufmanKelly M. EullVirginia R. CroninJoshua T. DambergRachell L. HenningContact UsCOVID-19
763.560.5700
866.211.4311
Make A Payment
HomeEmployment
FAQs
Testimonials
Blog
Newsletter Sign-up
About UsFirm HistoryCommunity InvolvementNewsEventsFor BusinessesCorporate LawConstruction LawCreditor's RightsEmployment LawLicensingNonprofit LawCommercial Real EstateTrademarks & CopyrightsLitigationFor IndividualsFamily Law and DivorceElder LawEstate PlanningResidential Real EstateAttorneysJames E. SnoxellSteven M. GraffunderJeffrey A. BergMark V. SteffensonCraig T. DokkenSusan T. Peterson-LerdahlChad E. HendersonDebra NelsonTifanne WolterAdam J. KaufmanKelly M. EullVirginia R. CroninJoshua T. DambergRachell L. HenningContact UsCOVID-19
Make A Payment
763.560.5700
866.211.4311
About UsFirm HistoryCommunity InvolvementNewsEventsFor BusinessesCorporate LawConstruction LawCreditor's RightsEmployment LawLicensingNonprofit LawCommercial Real EstateTrademarks & CopyrightsLitigationFor IndividualsFamily Law and DivorceElder LawEstate PlanningResidential Real EstateAttorneysJames E. SnoxellSteven M. GraffunderJeffrey A. BergMark V. SteffensonCraig T. DokkenSusan T. Peterson-LerdahlChad E. HendersonDebra NelsonTifanne WolterAdam J. KaufmanKelly M. EullVirginia R. CroninJoshua T. DambergRachell L. HenningContact UsCOVID-19
Make A Payment
763.560.5700
866.211.4311
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Henningson & Snoxell, Ltd. ® Privacy PolicyInformation Gathering.
Henningson & Snoxell, Ltd. (hereinafter “H&S” or “this firm” and sometimes “us” or “our”) describes how H&S handles information about you that is personally identifiable. Please contact this firm’s administrator if you have any questions or concerns about any aspect of this policy.H&S may obtain information about you in various ways, some of which are;You giving this firm information, including, without limitation, information you provide by filling out any forms we may provide, registering for any events, programs or seminars we are involved with, or in the course of your dealings with us. None of said provided information is tied to other personal information you may provide to this firm.You automatically give this firm information by browsing H&S’s website, downloading anything from that website or that we otherwise offer or present to you, and by sending or receiving e-mail messages from this firm or any of its personnel. Such automatically provided information includes, without limitation, the name of the domain and host from which you access the internet, the browser software you use, your operating system, and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to the H&S website.
Depending upon the nature of your relationship with this firm or the type of case you may engage H&S to represent you; this firm may seek, use, and keep both public and nonpublic personal information in connection with the matter at hand from other sources.
No “Sale” of Your Personal Information.
H&S does not sell or rent your personal information to any third party.
H&S Use of Your Personal Information.
This firm gathers, keeps, and may use the personal information you provide for use in connection with any legal services this firm may provide to you, any H&S event, program or seminar you might sign up for or participate in, this firm’s data base and record-keeping, this firm’s marketing, improving the firm’s website, systems and practices, in connection with any legal work this firm may do for you, and in response to any legal obligation we may have such as in response to a Court order. If you are a client of this firm, we may disclose your personal information to third parties if and only to the extent doing so is required or necessary in the course of your lawsuit or other legal matter you engage this firm to represent you.
Without limiting the scope of the preceding paragraph, H&S may disclose your personal information to its attorneys,
staff, and, subject to professional rules of conduct, service providers or suppliers in the course of said parties providing this firm their business, supply, professional, or technical services. H&S may also disclose your personal information to others assisting you or this firm with a client engagement (such as an accountant, consultant or expert) and to courts, other government agencies, opposing counsel, potential witnesses, and other outside parties as may be necessary to accomplish the purpose of a client engagement. We may also disclose nonpublic personal information, or any other information, if needed to defend this firm against a client’s claims, collect a fee, and otherwise as may be required or allowed by law or court order.Marketing Communications and “Opt-Out” Right.
H&S may also send you information, marketing materials, newsletters, and notices by e-mail or postal mail to one or more of the e-mail and postal mail addresses you disclose to us. You may decline to receive the same by giving us written notice that says you do not wish to receive such general communications. Said “opt out” notice can be sent to officemanager@hennsnoxlaw.com, by calling 763.560.5700 during normal business hours and explicitly communicating your opt-out request to either our receptionist or firm administrator, or by a mailed or personally delivered written notice signed by you and addressed to this firm at its mail address shown at the end of this Privacy Policy. Securing Your Personal Information.
Keeping your personal information secure is important to this firm, and we have put in place systems designed to protect the privacy of your personal information.
These systems include anti-virus software, “firewalls”, policies and procedures regarding operational matters.
In addition, we recommend you be careful about protecting your personal information and disclose no more personal information than necessary.
Ask us any time you have any concerns or questions about disclosing your personal information to us for any reason or to others in connection with any legal matter where we represent you.Even with the safeguards we have put in place to help protect the security of your personal information, breaches of information security are possible, especially in connection with information sent over the internet or stored by electronic means or in hard copy form. We encourage you to learn about the risks associated with disclosing personal information, read privacy policies (like this one) that third parties you do business with give you, and take such privacy protection and security measures as you determine are appropriate for you.Cookies.
A cookie is a small text file that can be placed on your computer's hard drive when accessing a website. The third party that hosts the H&S website reports the site does not use cookies, but keep in mind cookies may be used at sites accessible through links on this firm's website.Links to Other Websites.
This firm is not responsible for the information, practices or privacy policies of websites operated by others that may be linked to or from this firm's website or that this firm may tell you about. Should you decide to access a third party's website that may be linked to or from this firm's web site or that this firm may introduce to you, we suggest you familiarize yourself with that website's privacy policy.Questions.
Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this firm’s Privacy Policy or any aspect of how we collect, use, or keep your personal information. You can contact our firm administrator by calling 763.560.5700, by e-mail sent to officemanager@hennsnoxlaw.com, or by postal mail sent to this firm at its address shown at the end of this Privacy Policy.Accuracy of Information.
We try to keep our records accurate and will make appropriate corrections when you notify us.
Please let us know right away if there is incorrect information in any statements or other communications that you receive from us.Other Privacy Policy Terms.
This firm may change its policies regarding your personal information at any time. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will be shown on this firm’s website (www.hennsnoxlaw.com). The most current revision date is July 21, 2016. Keep this notice for your records. This notice and the policies it references are not intended to constitute an offer or an agreement, and in no event shall be deemed as an offer or as an agreement, of any kind on our part or to impose any duty or obligation of any kind upon us except as and to the extent expressly required by law.
We highly recommend the firm of Henningson and Snoxell and their seminars.
We value quality and excellence in service and that is what Henningson and Snoxell have provided for us.
Most importantly, they have helped in giving us peace of mind, and in today’s world that is important.
View Testimonials
Questions? Contact Our Law Office Today.
Contact Us
Sign up for Our NewsletterSubmit your email address to stay in touch with Henningson & Snoxell!
Latest News
View Blog
Peace of Mind for the Frontline
Free Incapacity Documents Now Through February, 2021 for All Healthcare Workers Minnesota, and our country at large, has been facing a healthcare crisis because of the coronavirus pandemic. COVID-19 continues to challenge our hosp… View Full Story
The Boy Scouts of America, Bankruptcy, & its Impact on Host Sites
The Boy Scouts of America “(BSA”) filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy on February 18, 2020 in the Federal Bankruptcy Court in the State of Delaware. This filing apparently occurred because of sexual abuse claims made against BSA. This… View Full Story
Elder Law Concierge Services
Adult children with elderly parents are experiencing stress like never before. They are often caught between raising their own children, working demanding jobs, and navigating their aging parents’ complicated situations and needs.… View Full Story
Henningson & Snoxell, Ltd.
Copyright © Henningson & Snoxell, Ltd.
